<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="notation">The notation is used to name the different possible movements in the layers of the cube to ease communication.</string>
    <string name="not">Notation</string>
    <string name="parts">Parts of the cube</string>
    <string name="edges">Edges</string>
    <string name="corners">Corners</string>
    <string name="centers">Centers</string>
    <string name="s1">1. White cross</string>
    <string name="s2">2. White corners</string>
    <string name="s3">3. Second layer</string>
    <string name="s4">4. Yellow cross</string>
    <string name="s5">5. Yellow edges on their correct places</string>
    <string name="s6">6. Yellow corners on their correct places</string>
    <string name="s7">7. Route yellow corners</string>
    <string name="wt2">Final goal: to make a cross in which the four edges of the cross matches with the color of the sided centers.</string>
    <string name="wt3">\"Adress all the white edges to the white center face. \"</string>
    <string name="wt4">Rotate the layer until at least two edges fit with the sided centers color.</string>
    <string name="wt5">"R' U' R U R'"</string>
    <string name="wt6">"F U2 F' U2 F"</string>
    <string name="wt7">Now you could face two alternatives to swap the two remaining edges.</string>
    <string name="wt8">Done!!</string>
    <string name="languages">Languages</string>
    <string name="wc4">white on left \nD\' R\' D R </string>
    <string name="wc5">white on right \nR\' D\' R</string>
    <string name="wc6">white on bottom \nR\' D2 R D R\' D\' R </string>
    <string name="wc2">Final goal.</string>
    <string name="wc8">Move the white corner under the spot where it is supposed to be.</string>
    <string name="wc9">And repeat for all the corners.</string>
    <string name="wc3">Now you can face 3 alternatives</string>
    <string name="notation2">A letter implies a single clockwise turn, a letter followed by \' means counter-clockwise turn and a letter followed by a number 2 means two turns.</string>
    <string name="centers2">"The centers do not move, they keep always in the same position, white opposite to yellow, red opposite to orange and blue opposite to green"</string>
    <string name="wt9">The red arrows indicate the two pieces that are swap and the letters indicate the movements that must be made following the notations that we have seen in the first section.</string>
    <string name="wc10">If you need to take a corner to put it somewhere else or it is in place but misdirected you have to do: R\' D\' R  to move it out.</string>
    <string name="e2">Put an edge that has to go to the second layer on top of a center with the same color</string>
    <string name="e3">If you need to take an edge to put it somewhere else or it is in place but misdirected you have to do: U R U\' R\' U\' F\' U F  to move it out</string>
    <string name="e4">If you need the edge to go to the right \nU R U\' R\' U\' F\' U F</string>
    <string name="e5">If you need the edge to go to the left \nU\' L\' U L U F U\' F\'</string>
    <string name="e6">Now you can have two situations </string>
    <string name="e7">Put the white face underneath</string>
    <string name="g2">If you have a point do the algorithm and you will get an L</string>
    <string name="g3">If you have an L do the algorithm and you will get a line</string>
    <string name="g4">If you have a line do the algorithm and you will get a cross</string>
    <string name="g5">Watch the edges, and check if you have: a point, an L shape, a line shape or you already have a cross \nAlgorithm: F R U R\' U\' F\'</string>
    <string name="a2">Rotate the layer until only one edge fits with the color of a center and do R U R\' U R U2 R\' until they all fit (can be once or twice)  If you can not fit just one edge do the algorithm and try again</string>
    <string name="l1">Final goal, put all the corners of the last layer in the right place, they do not need to be well oriented.</string>
    <string name="l2">Find a corner that is in the right place, put it to the right and do U R U\' L\' U R\' U\' L until all the corners are in the correct place (do it once or twice)  If there is no corner in the right place do the algorithm and look again.</string>
    <string name="f1">Now you just need to orient, put one of the corners that is not oriented up-right and do R\' D\' R D (do it two or four times as needed) until the corner is oriented, now with movements of U, U\' or U2 (DO NOT rotate the whole cube) put another corner that is not oriented and repeat the former movement. \n\nWhile doing this step it might seem that you have messed up the cube, do not worry.</string>
    <string name="f2">Let\'s see an something.</string>
    <string name="f3">Do R\' D\' R D twice but as the corner is not oriented we repeat the movement twice</string>
    <string name="f4">Do U2 to put the other corner to the right and do R\' D\' R D twice and U2 to finish the cube</string>
    <string name="ca">Categories</string>
    <string name="ca1">World Records are the following (up to September 2017) </string>
    <string name="re1">Resources</string>
    <string name="mjoc">Minigame</string>
    <string name="Crono">Timer</string>
    <string name="re2">WCA: the official ranking.</string>
    <string name="re3">cstimer: specialized Timer.</string>
    <string name="re4">Cubecomps: results of competitions in progress.</string>
    <string name="crono1">Start</string>
    <string name="crono2">Pause</string>
    <string name="rest">Restart</string>
</resources>